callwiki.com 2012-11-12

# 

PRIVACY POLICY

In order to protect your privacy this policy explains our policies on:

I. EXTERNAL LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

You may find a variety of hyperlinks on our website which link to other, external, websites, which may have different policies than our website. Upon leaving our website, through any external link, you should examine their Privacy Policy to be informed of the way in which they will use your information. Any policies, information or practices on third-party websites are beyond our control and we bear no responsibility in their use.

II. INFORMATION GATHERED

While we use cookies in order to improve your experience on this website and to personalize content, no personal information is gathered through our use of cookies. 

If you would not like your information to be collected by cookies on our site, most internet browsers allow you to either turn off cookies or give you the option to reject or accept them. You should be aware that disabling cookies from our website will prevent us from providing you with some services.

We advise you to use discretion in supplying personal information (avoid the publication of your personal email address or phone number) for publication on our website as all information provided is publicly available.

III. ADVERTISING BY THIRD PARTIES

Third-party advertising may be used on this website. Information such as pixel tags, cookies, or a variety of other independently collected information may be collected by these companies. They will not collect your name, telephone number or email address. They may use this information, as well as information collected about your use of this website and others (such as cookies, the date and time of the advertisement, and your IP address), to provide advertising which may be of interest to you. The collection and use of this information is not under our control.

CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY

In the event this Privacy Policy is modified it will be reflected in an updated version of this document.
